("Rap God" by Eminem)
♪ Look ♪
♪ I was gonna go easy on you ♪
♪ And not to hurt
your feelings ♪
♪ But I'm only going to
get this one chance ♪
♪ Six minutes ♪
♪ Something's wrong,
I can feel it ♪
♪ Six minutes, Slim
Shady, you're on ♪
♪ Just a feeling I've got ♪
♪ Like something's
about to happen ♪
♪ But I don't know what ♪
♪ If that means what
I think it means ♪
♪ We're in trouble,
big trouble ♪
♪ And if he is as
bananas as you say ♪
♪ I'm not taking any chances ♪
♪ You were just what
the doc ordered ♪
♪ I'm beginnin' to feel
like a Rap God, Rap God ♪
♪ All my people from the front
to the back nod, back nod ♪
♪ Now who thinks their
arms are long enough ♪
♪ To slap box, slap box? ♪
♪ They said I rap like a
robot, so call me Rapbot ♪
♪ But for me to rap like a
computer must be in my genes ♪
♪ I got a laptop
in my back pocket ♪
♪ My pen'll go off
when I half-cock it ♪
♪ Got a fat knot from
that rap profit ♪
♪ Made a living and
a killing off it ♪
♪ Ever since Bill Clinton
was still in office ♪
♪ With Monica Lewinsky
feeling on his nut-sack ♪
♪ I'm an MC still as honest ♪
♪ But as rude and indecent
as all hell syllables ♪
♪ Killaholic ♪
♪ Kill 'em all with ♪
♪ This slickety, gibbedy,
hibbedy hip hop ♪
♪ You don't really wanna
get into a pissing match ♪
♪ With this rappidy brat ♪
♪ Packing a Mac in
the back of the Ac ♪
♪ Backpack rap crap,
yap-yap, yackety-yac ♪
♪ And at the exact same
time, I attempt these ♪
♪ Lyrical acrobat stunts
while I'm practicin' that ♪
♪ I'll still be able to
break a motherfuckin' table ♪
♪ Over the back of a
couple of faggots ♪
♪ And crack it in half ♪
♪ Only realized it was
ironic, I was signed to ♪
♪ Aftermath after the fact ♪
♪ How could I not blow? ♪
♪ All I do is drop F-bombs,
feel my wrath of attack ♪
♪ Rappers are havin' a rough
time period, here's a maxipad ♪
♪ It's actually disastrously
bad for the wack ♪
♪ While I'm masterfully
constructing this
masterpiece as ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm beginnin' to
feel like a Rap God, Rap God ♪
♪ All my people from the front
to the back nod, back nod ♪
♪ Now who thinks their
arms are long enough ♪
♪ To slap box, slap box? ♪
♪ Let me show you
maintainin' this shit ♪
♪ Ain't that hard, that hard ♪
♪ Everybody wants the
key and the secret ♪
♪ To rap immortality
like I have got ♪
♪ Well, to be truthful
the blueprint's ♪
♪ Simply rage and
youthful exuberance ♪
♪ Everybody loves to
root for a nuisance ♪
♪ Hit the earth
like an asteroid ♪
♪ Did nothing but shoot
for the moon since ♪
♪ Pew! ♪
♪ MCs get taken to
school with this music ♪
♪ 'Cause I use it as a
vehicle to "bus the rhyme" ♪
♪ Now I lead a new
school full of students ♪
♪ Me? I'm a product of
Rakim, Lakim Shabazz, 2Pac ♪
♪ N.W.A., Cube, hey Doc,
Ren, Yella, Eazy, thank you ♪
♪ They got Slim inspired
enough to one day grow up ♪
♪ Blow up and be in a position ♪
♪ To meet Run-DMC and
induct them into the ♪
♪ Motherfuckin' Rock
and Roll Hall of Fame ♪
♪ Even though I'll
walk in the church ♪
♪ And burst in a
ball of flames ♪
♪ Only Hall of Fame
I'll be inducted in ♪
♪ Is the alcohol of fame ♪
♪ On the wall of shame ♪
♪ You fags think
it's all a game ♪
♪ 'Til I walk a
flock of flames ♪
♪ Off of a plank and ♪
♪ Tell me what in the
fuck are you thinkin'? ♪
♪ Little gay-lookin' boy ♪
♪ So gay I can barely say it ♪
♪ With a straight face,
lookin' boy (Ha!) ♪
♪ You witnessing a mass-occur) ♪
♪ Like you're watching
a church gathering ♪
♪ Take place, lookin' boy ♪
♪ "Oy vey, that boy's gay!" ♪
♪ That's all they
say, lookin' boy ♪
♪ You get a thumbs
up, pat on the back ♪
♪ And a "way to go" from your
label everyday, lookin' boy ♪
♪ Hey, lookin' boy! What
you say, lookin' boy? ♪
♪ I got a "hell yeah"
from Dre, lookin' boy ♪
♪ I'ma work for
everything I have ♪
♪ Never asked nobody for shit ♪
♪ Get outta my
face, lookin' boy ♪
♪ Basically, boy, you're
never gonna be capable ♪
♪ Or keepin' up with the
same pace, lookin' boy ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm beginnin' to
feel like a Rap God, Rap God ♪
♪ All my people from the front
to the back nod, back nod ♪
♪ The way I'm racin'
around the track ♪
♪ Call me NASCAR, NASCAR ♪
♪ Dale Earnhardt of the trailer
park, the White Trash God ♪
♪ Kneel before General Zod ♪
♪ This planet's Krypton ♪
♪ No, Asgard, Asgard ♪
♪ So you be Thor
and I'll be Odin ♪
♪ You rodent, I'm omnipotent ♪
♪ Let off then I'm reloadin' ♪
♪ Immediately with
these bombs I'm totin' ♪
♪ And I should not be woken ♪
♪ I'm the walking' dead, but
I'm just a talkin' head ♪
♪ A zombie floatin' ♪
♪ But I got your
mom deep-throatin' ♪
♪ I'm out my Ramen noodle ♪
♪ We have nothin'
in common, poodle ♪
♪ Poodle, I'm a doberman ♪
♪ Pinch yourself in the
arm and pay homage, pupil ♪
♪ It's me, my honesty's brutal ♪
♪ But it's honestly futile ♪
♪ If I don't utilize
what I do though ♪
♪ For good at least
once in a while ♪
♪ So I wanna make sure
somewhere in this ♪
♪ Chicken scratch I scribble
and doodle enough rhymes to ♪
♪ Maybe to try to help get some
people through tough times ♪
♪ But I gotta keep a few
punchlines just in case ♪
♪ 'Cause even you unsigned ♪
♪ Rappers are hungry lookin'
at me like it's lunchtime ♪
♪ I know there was a
time where once I ♪
♪ Was king of the underground ♪
♪ But I still rap like I'm
on my Pharoahe Monch grind ♪
♪ So I crunch rhymes, but
sometimes when you combine ♪
♪ Appeal with the
skin color of mine ♪
♪ You get too big and
here they come tryin' to ♪
♪ Censor you like
that one line ♪
♪ I said on "I'm Back" from
the Mathers LP1 when I ♪
♪ Tried to say I'll take
seven kids from Columbine ♪
♪ Put 'em all in a line, add
an AK-47, a revolver and a 9 ♪
♪ See if I get away with it ♪
♪ Now that I ain't as
big as I was, but I'm ♪
♪ Morphin' into an immortal,
comin' through the portal ♪
♪ You're stuck in a time
warp from 2004 though ♪
♪ And I don't know what the
fuck that you rhyme for ♪
♪ You're pointless as Rapunzel
with fuckin' cornrows ♪
♪ You write normal?
Fuck being normal ♪
♪ And I just bought a new
raygun from the future ♪
♪ Just to come and shoot ya ♪
♪ Like when Fabolous
made Ray J mad ♪
♪ 'Cause Fab said he looked
like a fag at Mayweather's pad ♪
♪ Singin' to a man
while he played piano ♪
♪ Man, oh man, that
was a 24/7 special ♪
♪ On the cable channel ♪
♪ So Ray J went straight
to the radio station ♪
♪ The very next day ♪
♪ "Hey, Fab, I'ma kill you!" ♪
♪ Lyrics comin' at you
at supersonic speed ♪
♪ J.J. Fad ♪
♪ Uh, summa-lumma, dooma-lumma,
you assumin' I'm a human ♪
♪ What I gotta do to get it
through to you I'm superhuman ♪
♪ Innovative and
I'm made of rubber ♪
♪ So that anything you
say is ricochetin' ♪
♪ Off of me and it'll
glue to you and ♪
♪ I'm devastating, more
than ever demonstrating ♪
♪ How to give a
motherfuckin' audience ♪
♪ A feeling like it's
levitating, never fading ♪
♪ And I know that the
haters are forever waiting ♪
♪ For the day that they
can say I fell off ♪
♪ They'll be celebrating ♪
♪ 'Cause I know the way
to get 'em motivated ♪
♪ I make elevating music,
you make elevator music ♪
♪ "Oh, he's too mainstream." ♪
♪ Well, that's what they
do when they get jealous ♪
♪ They confuse it ♪
♪ "It's not hip hop, it's pop" ♪
♪ 'Cause I found a
hella way to fuse it ♪
♪ With rock, shock
rap with Doc ♪
♪ Throw on Lose Yourself
and make 'em lose it ♪
♪ "I don't know how to
make songs like that" ♪
♪ "I don't know
what words to use" ♪
♪ Let me know when
it occurs to you ♪
♪ While I'm rippin' any
one of these verses ♪
♪ That verses you ♪
♪ It's curtains, I'm
inadvertently hurtin' you ♪
♪ How many verses
I gotta murder to ♪
♪ Prove that if you
were half as nice ♪
♪ Your songs you could
sacrifice virgins too?! ♪
♪ Ugh, school
flunkie, pill junkie ♪
♪ But look at the accolades
these skills brung me ♪
♪ Full of myself,
but still hungry ♪
♪ I bully myself 'cause I make
me do what I put my mind to ♪
♪ And I'm a million
leagues above you ♪
♪ Ill when I speak in tongues ♪
♪ But it's still
tongue-in-cheek, fuck you ♪
♪ I'm drunk, so Satan,
take the fucking wheel ♪
♪ I'ma sleep in the front seat ♪
♪ Bumpin' Heavy D and the Boyz,
still "Chunky, but funky" ♪
♪ But in my head
there's something ♪
♪ I can feel tugging
and struggling ♪
♪ Angels fight with devils and ♪
♪ Here's what they
want from me ♪
♪ They're askin' me to eliminate
some of the women hate ♪
♪ But if you take
into consideration ♪
♪ The bitter hatred I have ♪
♪ Then you may be
a little patient ♪
♪ And more sympathetic
to the situation ♪
♪ And understand
the discrimination ♪
♪ But fuck it, life's
handin' you lemons? ♪
♪ Make lemonade then! ♪
♪ But if I can't
batter the women ♪
♪ How the fuck am I supposed
to bake them a cake then?! ♪
♪ Don't mistake him for Satan ♪
♪ It's a fatal mistake if you
think I need to be overseas ♪
♪ And take a vacation
to trip a broad ♪
♪ And make her fall
on her face and ♪
♪ Don't be a retard ♪
♪ Be a king? Think not ♪
♪ Why be a king when
you can be a God? ♪